<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Wwe Page</title>
    <link>https://github.com/IsaacRamosDaw/wwe</link>
    <description>wwe Stars</description>
    <copyright>2024 @WWE. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <item>
      <title>Superstar Ston Cold</title>
      <link>https://wwereact-bab2d.web.app/fighters</link>
      <description>Stone Cold Steve Austin, known for his rebellious persona and iconic catchphrase "Austin 3:16," is a legendary figure in WWE history. Renowned for his intense brawls and unparalleled charisma, Austin revolutionized professional wrestling during the Attitude Era, becoming a multiple-time WWE Champion and a symbol of anti-establishment defiance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rock</title>
      <link>https://wwereact-bab2d.web.app/fighters</link>
      <description>Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson, a charismatic powerhouse, transcended WWE to become a Hollywood icon. Known for his electrifying performances and signature eyebrow raise, he is a multiple-time WWE Champion and one of the most beloved figures in entertainment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Undertaker</title>
      <link>https://wwereact-bab2d.web.app/fighters</link>
      <description>With an ominous presence and unmatched longevity, The Undertaker is a WWE legend. Renowned for his eerie persona, streak of WrestleMania victories, and unmatched intimidation factor, he remains one of the most respected and feared competitors in wrestling history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John cena</title>
      <link>https://wwereact-bab2d.web.app/fighters</link>
      <description> John Cena, the face of WWE for over a decade, is a 16-time World Champion and pop culture phenomenon. With his mantra of "Hustle, Loyalty, and Respect," Cena became a symbol of perseverance and a role model for millions worldwide, both in and out of the ring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hulk Hogan</title>
      <link>https://wwereact-bab2d.web.app/fighters</link>
      <description>A true icon of professional wrestling, Hulk Hogan defined an era with his larger-than-life persona and unmatched charisma. As a multiple-time WWE Champion and the centerpiece of Hulkamania, he transcended the sport to become a global phenomenon and a household name</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triple H</title>
      <link>https://wwereact-bab2d.web.app/fighters</link>
      <description>Triple H, also known as "The Game," is a WWE Hall of Famer and one of the most influential figures behind the scenes. As a 14-time World Champion and master strategist, he dominated WWE both as a competitor and as an executive, shaping the landscape of sports entertainment for decades</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ric Flair</title>
      <link>https://wwereact-bab2d.web.app/fighters</link>
      <description>"The Nature Boy" Ric Flair, a 16-time World Champion, epitomizes the essence of professional wrestling. With his flamboyant style, unmatched in-ring skill, and iconic catchphrase "Woo," Flair set the standard for excellence and became one of the most celebrated figures in the history of the sport</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>